jobsinworld.com 2019-03-24

# Privacy Policy | JobsinWorld Kerala - JobsinWorld.com

These days, we all need to be smart about the way we use our own personal data. JobsinWorld has always been on the forefront of Privacy issues, and we're constantly refining our Security Policy to ensure that you can get your job done all on your own terms and completely anonymously if you so desire. So that you can be smarter about the way you manage your career, JobsinWorld helps you to strive to provide the safest possible environment for you to search and apply to jobs. This privacy policy describes how your personal information is collected, used, shared, and secured, as well as your choices regarding use and access of your personal information. 

PERSONAL INFORMATION  
JobsinWorld collects personal information from users on a voluntary basis only. This information allows us to provide users with private and secure areas to post and modify their original content on our site (e.g., jobs and resumes).JobsinWorld is committed to protecting the privacy of our users, and strives to provide a safe user experience. This privacy policy describes how your personal information is collected, used, shared, and secured, as well as your choices regarding use, access, and correction of your personal information.

By using this site, you agree to the collection, use and transfer of your data as described in this Privacy Policy. By accepting the policy at the time of registration, you expressly approve and consent to our collection, storage, use and disclosure of your personal information as described in this Policy and terms and conditions.As this may result in unsolicited messages from third parties for which JobsinWorld is not responsible. Also, you may have arrived at this web site by following a link from a JobsinWorld newspaper affiliate or other affiliate. If so, please be aware that JobsinWorld may share your information with that affiliate and the affiliate may use the information consistent with its privacy policy instead of this one.

If you do not want your information to be collected, used, and transferred as described by this policy, you may revoke your consent to our Privacy Policy. To revoke your consent, please contact us. If you revoke your consent, your account and profile information will be removed from our website.

Credit Card Security  
JobsinWorld employs the highest level of encryption for secure credit card transactions. You are responsible for ensuring that your log-in credentials (your username and password) are kept confidential.Moreover, one of our primary purposes is to provide you with a platform to broadcast the information in your resume and profile widely and to maximize your career opportunities. Accordingly, such an environment does present a risk that unauthorized third parties will view this data. Further, your resume should not contain any sensitive data including personality profiles or data that you would not want made public. You should be aware that resumes you complete at your current place of work may be monitored by your current employer.When you place an order online at JobsinWorld, your credit card information is protected through the use of encryption, such as the artificial intelligence, which makes it difficult for your credit card information to be intercepted or stolen while being transmitted. JobsinWorld uses a service company to process its credit card transactions. JobsinWorld has implemented technical measures designed to secure your personal information from unauthorized access, use, alteration or disclosure. Notwithstanding such measures, the Internet is an open system and we cannot guarantee that unauthorized third parties will never be able to defeat those measures or use your personal information for improper purposes. 

You should be aware that resumes and profiles may be monitored by your current employer.

When you place an order online at JobsinWorld, your credit card information is encrypted with industry standard encryption.

ABOUT COOKIES  
We use cookie as a text file stored on your computer. Cookies store bits of information that we use to help make our site work, cookies help us to improve your experience on this site. A cookie can’t run any code and don’t contain viruses. No one can read our cookies except us, at JobsinWorld, we use cookies only for the protection and convenience of our users.Certain cookies are essential to the proper function of this site.

Cookies enable us to serve secure pages to our users without asking them to sign in repeatedly. If a user's system is idle for more than an hour, however, the cookie will expire, forcing the user to sign in again to continue their session. This prevents unauthorized access to the user's information while they are away from their computer, our third-party advertisers may place or recognize a unique "cookie" on your browser.We don’t track your personal activities when you’re not on JobsinWorld sites unless you click on one of our ads on those sites;we use analytics cookies to help us understand what content is most useful to our visitors.

Types of Cookies We Use  
Security: These cookies allow us to secure access to your account.

Preference: These cookies are used to store your preferences like language choice and display of job search results.

Analytics: We track site traffic patterns so we can identify popular site content and potential site problems.

Site features: We track which jobs you look at so we can show you more jobs like those.

Advertising: We use non-identifiable information about you to show you advertising on our site.

ADVERTISING  
We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use information about you and your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements on this site and other sites about goods and services of interest to you.

JobsinWorld shows targeted job ads to you through our web site. These ads appear on JobsinWorld sites and on third party web sites. Targeted job advertising is based on your interests, which are inferred from certain demographic and geographic data and the search terms you enter when using JobsinWorld and is not linked to your personally identifiable information without your permission. JobsinWorld allows third-parties to show you ads on JobsinWorld. To determine which targeted ads you see, we use third-party services to manage the behavioral, demographic, geographic and personal information we collect or infer about you. We may combine this information with certain other non-personal information we get from third-parties, including information about your interests, to serve more relevant ads to you. JobsinWorld does not provide any personal information to the third party advertisers on our site unless you choose to allow it. JobsinWorld has no control over, and is not responsible for, the practices of those third party advertisers. JobsinWorld encourages you to visit their web sites and review their privacy policies.

JOB POSTERS POSTING RULES  
Employers are solely responsible for their postings on JobsinWorld sites. JobsinWorld is not to be considered to be an employer with respect to your use of any JobsinWorld site and JobsinWorld shall not be responsible for any employment decisions, for whatever reason, made by any entity posting jobs on any JobsinWorld site.

You may not use your Documents to impersonate another person, living or dead, post false, inaccurate or misleading information, post advertisements or solicitations of business (including, but not limited to, Multi-Level Marketing (MLM) positions, Email Processors, "club memberships," distributorships, or anything requiring a monetary investment by the User); post chain letters or pyramid schemes; or post opinions or notices, commercial or otherwise.

You understand and acknowledge that if you cancel your employer account or your employer account is terminated, all your account information from JobsinWorld, including saved resumes may be deleted from JobsinWorld databases. Information may continue to be available for some period of time because of delays in propagating such deletion through JobsinWorld web servers.

A Job Posting May Not Contain:  
• Any hyperlinks, other than those specifically authorized by JobsinWorld.

• You may not use your Documents to impersonate another person, living or dead, post false, inaccurate or misleading information, post advertisements or solicitations of business (including, Multi-Level Marketing (MLM) positions, Email Processors, distributorships, or anything requiring a monetary investment by the User).

• Posting of chain letters or pyramid schemes or post opinions or notices, commercial or otherwise.

• Misleading, unreadable, or "hidden" keywords, repeated keywords or keywords that is irrelevant to the job opportunity being presented, as determined in JobsinWorld reasonable discretion.

• The names, logos or trademarks of unaffiliated companies other than those of your customer save where expressly agreed by JobsinWorld.

• The names of colleges, cities, states, towns or countries those are unrelated to the posting.

• More than one job or job description, more than one location, or more than one job category, unless the product so allows.

• Inaccurate, false, or misleading information; and material or links to material that exploits people in a sexual, violent or other manner, or solicits personal information from anyone under 18.

JOB SEEKER RULES  
When you register with JobsinWorld site, you will be asked to create an account and provide JobsinWorld with certain information including, without limitation, a valid email address.

Any profile you submit must be accurate and describe you, an individual person. The Profile requires standard fields to be completed and you may not include in these fields any telephone numbers, addresses, email addresses or other means of contacting you, other than your last name.

You acknowledge and agree that you are solely responsible for the form, content and accuracy of any resume or material contained therein placed by you on the JobsinWorld sites.

JobsinWorld reserves the right to offer third party services and products to you based on the preferences that you identify in your registration and at any time thereafter or you have agreed to receive, such offers may be made by JobsinWorld or by third parties.

You understand and acknowledge that you have no ownership rights in your account with JobsinWorld and the account can be terminated by JobsinWorld if required, all your account information from JobsinWorld, including Resumes, Profiles, Saved jobs, questionnaires may be deleted from JobsinWorld databases and will be removed from any public area of the JobsinWorld sites. Information may continue to be available for some period of time because of delays in propagating such deletion through JobsinWorld web servers. In addition, third parties may retain saved copies of your Information.

JobsinWorld reserves the right to delete your account and all of your Information after a significant duration of inactivity.

The jobs, resume database (“JobsinWorld Resume Database”) and other features of the JobsinWorld sites may be used only by individuals seeking career information and by seeking employees. In addition, JobsinWorld networking and profiles may be used by individuals for permitted personal networking purposes. Your use of the JobsinWorld services is also subject to any other contracts you may have with JobsinWorld. In the case of any conflict between these Terms and any contract you have with JobsinWorld, the terms of your contract will prevail. The term “post” as used herein shall mean information that you submit, publish or display on a JobsinWorld site.

You are responsible for maintaining the confidentiality of your Account, Profile and Passwords, as applicable. You may not share your password or other account access information with any other party, temporarily or permanently, and you shall be responsible for all uses of your JobsinWorld site registrations and passwords, whether or not authorized by you. You agree to immediately notify JobsinWorld of any unauthorized use of your Account, Profile or Passwords.

JobsinWorld makes no representations or guarantees regarding the truthfulness, accuracy, completeness, timeliness or reliability of any documents posted by users or of any other form of communication engaged in by users. All users should be aware, however, that when they voluntarily display or distribute personal information (such as email address or resume) that information can be collected and used by others. This may result in unsolicited messages from third parties for which JobsinWorld are not responsible.

YOU ASSUME ALL RESPONSIBILITY AND RISK FOR YOUR USE OF THE SITE, THE INTERNET GENERALLY, AND THE DOCUMENTS YOU POST OR ACCESS AND FOR YOUR CONDUCT ON AND OFF THE SITE.

### Terms and Conditions/Privacy Policy

The JobsinWorld services are defined as the applications and services offered by JobsinWorld, including an on-line service to post and search employment opportunities and including any application accessed through the Facebook Platform and/or any mobile or other interface that allows you to access such application (collectively, “JobsinWorld Services”). The JobsinWorld sites also allow users to create individual profiles, which may include personal information and to make these profiles. JobsinWorld may revise these Terms at any time by posting an updated version to this web page. You should visit this page periodically to review the most current Terms because they are binding on you.

Users who violate these Terms may have their access and use of the JobsinWorld sites suspended or terminated, at JobsinWorld discretion.

These Terms constitute a binding agreement between You and JobsinWorld, operating the Web site in which business is headquartered (“JobsinWorld”), and are deemed accepted by You each time that You use or access any JobsinWorld site or JobsinWorld services. If You do not accept the Terms stated here, do not use the JobsinWorld site and the JobsinWorld services.

OTHER PRIVACY FEATURES ON Jobsviewer  
You never need to provide data to search for jobs log in to JobsinWorld is always an optional task for you to take, although logging in does give you access to smarter job search tools such as other personal search agents and saved searches.

YOU NEVER NEED TO PROVIDE DATA TO APPLY FOR A JOB ON Jobsviewer  
When posting your resume, Jobsviewer offers you three privacy options. Standard posting will give you the most visibility to the broadest employer audience possible - but because your confidentiality is as important to us as it is to you, we also offer Anonymous and Private posting options.

POST A RESUME  
Posting your resume on JobsinWorld puts you in front of thousands of employers with open positions each day. When you post your resume by create a registration using your details like name, email address and password that you supply. When you return to the site in the future you will use that same email address and password to access and edit your existing resume.

RESUME PRIVACY OPTIONS  
We know that our job seekers have varying levels of comfort when it comes to posting their resume on the Internet. To accommodate the needs of all users, Jobsviewer has 3 levels of privacy from which you can choose.

STANDARD POSTING  
This option gives you the most visibility to the broadest employer audience possible by making your resume searchable in our VIP Resume Database.

ANONYMOUS POSTING  
You can also post to the public resume database without any of your contact information being displayed. (If you use this option be sure to remove your contact information from the body of the resume.) The anonymous option also allows you to only display selected pieces of contact information.

PRIVATE POSTING FOR APPLY ONLINE ONLY  
This option allows you to post your resume on Jobsviewer without having it searched by employers. The benefit is that you can quickly and easily apply for jobs without retyping your information.

YOUR GENERAL CONTACT INFORMATION  
Managing your privacy is as simple as selecting which pieces of your contact information are displayed. This is done in the section of the resume form called "Contact Information." Using option 3 above requires that you select the Apply Online Only option from the "Contact Information" section at the bottom of the edit form, as shown below.

If you see a questionable job posting or site activity, please report the suspected fraud to us using our feedback form. If you think you have been a victim of fraud, immediately report the committed fraud to your local police and contact us using our feedback form so steps can be taken for your safety.

>
